wamba.com 2010-08-30

# Wamba : Privacy

WAMBA PROJECT, S.L.

Privacy policy  

Wamba Project S.L., domiciled in Avenida Jaume III, 5, 4º B, Palma de Mallorca, CIF B57425399, is liable for the website wamba.com, the purpose of which is to offer online services oriented to provide different kinds of leisure through Internet, help the User to communicate with other users, creating a contact network, as well as to offer the User a space in Internet which allows him to share personal information, interests and hobbies, and also to listen to music and upload videos. Wamba also offers its Users a forum where they can communicate and express their opinions. The information each User shares about himself within the website, will serve to identify him.

By using the website, you become a User of the same (hereinafter “the User”) and accept all the terms and conditions included in this privacy policy as well as the General Terms and Conditions published by Wamba at the time the User has access to the web.

Our main concern is the protection of the personal information provided by the users and the way said information is handled by us will be explained in this privacy policy.

Wamba reserves the right to modify this privacy policy in order to abide by any modifications in current laws and court rulings. Any modifications will be announced through this page in advance. The use of our services once the modifications are announced will imply their acceptance.

Applicable legislation 

Wamba abides by the legislation in force in Spain and the European Union concerning personal information about users, particularly, by the Organic Law of Personal Data Protection and its development regulations. Thereby, we have taken the necessary technical and administrative measures to avoid the loss, misuse, modification, non-authorized access and theft of the personal data provided by users, taking into account the current state of technology, the nature of the data and the risks to which it is exposed.

Security 

Wamba has adopted the levels of safety for personal data protection demanded by the Development Regulations of the Organic Law 15/1999 for the protection of personal data (Royal Decree 1720/2007). Moreover, Wamba makes all efforts to install additional means and technical measures to avoid the loss, misuse, modification, non-authorized access and theft of the data provided by users.

However, any data transference through the Internet entails the risk of being intercepted. Wamba cannot assure that it will not happen, and therefore it will not be liable if it happened.

In those web services that require a registration as User, a password must be chosen. The User is liable for keeping the confidentiality of said password, as well as of any and all activities that take place during the session started with his username and password. The User undertakes to notify Wamba as soon as possible about the non-authorized use of his username and password or any other security failure. Wamba shall not be liable for any damages or losses that may arise from the non-fulfillment of the obligations undertaken by the User.

Data collection 

Wamba shall use the personal data provided by the user in order to offer the services requested by the User and to send communications related to the service, as well as a newsletter and news that may be considered interesting. In case the User does not request otherwise through the means available, Wamba shall send the User, even via email, commercial communications of its own or that belong to a third party.

The User who does not wish to receive the aforementioned newsletter shall specify so in the Registration Area. The User may not request not to receive other communications from Wamba, since they are necessary for the maintenance of the service.

Wamba shall not transfer the personal data provided by users to third parties without their prior consent.

The data provided shall be included in a personal data file duly registered with the Spanish Agency of Data Protection. The sending of personal data, including the image, implies the User accepts that it be included in said file.

Registration: in order to become a user of the Wamba social network or the forum, the User shall first create a user account. With that purpose, Wamba shall request the following information: name, email address, address, age, occupation, username and password.

Profile: once registered, the User may provide additional information, including interests, hobbies, photographs, etc. providing said information is voluntary, but it will allow the User to increase the number of contacts in his network. However, the User must be aware that the information included in his space may be seen by multiple users.

Information about contacts: in order to invite other people to join Wamba, the User will need to enter their names and email addresses. This information shall be used by Wamba to send the invitations, which shall include the message chosen by the User. Said information shall only be used to send the invitation.

All the information entered about the contacts shall be protected by the terms and conditions within this privacy policy.

The Users of Revistate! shall be aware that, although no registration in Wamba is required, the image is considered personal data and shall be part of a personal data file which abides by all the obligations established by regulations in force concerning data protection and that have been stated in this document.

Wamba has hired the hosting services of Eve1Servers, based in the United States, as well as the outsourcing it services of SX Networks, based in Uruguay. Said companies are in charge of personal data handling. Therefore, the transference of the User’s personal data to them is necessary for the providing of the service. By accepting this privacy policy, the User accepts that its personal information be transferred to the aforementioned companies. Wamba shall change its providers in the future and it shall inform the User about the identity of the new company in charge of his personal data.

Data publishing 

It shall be taken into account that all the information the User decides to make public shall be visible for all the Users of Wamba, including the images.

The other users of Wamba shall be able to access the information the User decided to make public. The User may change or delete said information at any time.

In case the images uploaded by the User include other people, the User shall request the permission of said people to display the images in Wamba. Wamba shall not be liable for the content of the images uploaded by the User.

Contact 

Wamba shall communicate with the User via email sent to the email address included in the registration data; and via messages published in the website.

Minors 

The services provided by Wamba are aimed for users **over 14**. People under 14 are not authorized to use the services and shall not, therefore, provide Wamba with their personal information. 

IP addresses and cookies 

Due to communication protocols used within the Internet, whenever a User visits Wamba’s website, Wamba automatically receives the IP (Internet Protocol) address assigned to the User by his Access Provider. The registration of said IP address has internal purposes only, such as access statistics. The IP address for the same User is different from one Internet connection to the other, and therefore it is not possible to track navigation habits for a specific User.

Wamba may use cookies when the User navigates through its site and web pages. The cookies may be used within the web are only associated to the browser in a specific computer (an anonymous user), and they do not provide by themselves any personal data about the User. Cookies are only used for internal purposes, such as access statistics. The cookies used cannot read the cookie files created by other providers or websites. The User may setup its browser so as to be warned about cookies and to prevent cookies from being installed in his computer. The User may read the instructions and manuals of his browser in order to obtain more information.

Links 

This website contains links to other websites. The User must be aware that Wamba shall not be liable for the privacy policies and contents provided by said websites. The User shall be aware that using one of said links implies leaving Wamba and the User shall read the privacy policy of other websites that collect personal data.

This privacy policy shall only apply to the personal data collected through this website.

Registration modification and cancellation 

Those Users who wish to modify their personal information or cancel their registration, may easily correct, update or delete their personal data by entering the Registration Area.

If the User wishes to make use of his access, modification, opposition or cancellations rights, he may contact Wamba at: Wamba Project, SL, Avenida Jaume III, 5, 4ºB, Palma de Mallorca, or send an email to [privacy@wamba.com](mailto:privacy@wamba.com).

Note 

This website uses the audience measurement tools provided by Nielsen/NetRatings, which allow to analyze the profile and behavior of anonymous visitors, with the aim to improve the site, said measurement uses third party cookies; the privacy policy of the aforementioned company can be accessed [here](http://www.nielsen-online.com/privacy.jsp?section=leg_scs&region=sp).
